<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TEI xml:space="preserve" xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" 
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" 
xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0 https://raw.githubusercontent.com/kermitt2/grobid/master/grobid-home/schemas/xsd/Grobid.xsd"
 xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink">
	<teiHeader xml:lang="en">
		<fileDesc>
			<titleStmt>
				<title level="a" type="main">2024 Level III Topic Outlines Economics LEARNING OUTCOMES Capital Market Expectations, Part 1: Framework and Macro Considerations</title>
			</titleStmt>
			<publicationStmt>
				<publisher/>
				<availability status="unknown"><licence/></availability>
			</publicationStmt>
			<sourceDesc>
				<biblStruct>
					<analytic>
						<title level="a" type="main">2024 Level III Topic Outlines Economics LEARNING OUTCOMES Capital Market Expectations, Part 1: Framework and Macro Considerations</title>
					</analytic>
					<monogr>
						<imprint>
							<date/>
						</imprint>
					</monogr>
					<idno type="MD5">9680F98C1504134C55D67425E27190A1</idno>
				</biblStruct>
			</sourceDesc>
		</fileDesc>
		<encodingDesc>
			<appInfo>
				<application version="0.8.0" ident="GROBID" when="2024-02-15T18:29+0000">
					<desc>GROBID - A machine learning software for extracting information from scholarly documents</desc>
					<ref target="https://github.com/kermitt2/grobid"/>
				</application>
			</appInfo>
		</encodingDesc>
		<profileDesc>
			<abstract>
				<p>□ discuss the role of, and a framework for, capital market expectations in the portfolio management process □ discuss challenges in developing capital market forecasts □ explain how exogenous shocks may affect economic growth trends □ discuss the application of economic growth trend analysis to the formulation of capital market expectations □ compare major approaches to economic forecasting □ discuss how business cycles affect short-and long-term expectations □ explain the relationship of inflation to the business cycle and the implications of inflation for cash, bonds, equity, and real estate returns □ discuss the effects of monetary and fiscal policy on business cycles □ interpret the shape of the yield curve as an economic predictor and discuss the relationship between the yield curve and fiscal and monetary policy □ identify and interpret macroeconomic, interest rate, and exchange rate linkages between economies Capital Market Expectations, Part 2: Forecasting Asset Class Returns The candidate should be able to: □ discuss approaches to setting expectations for fixed-income returns □ discuss risks faced by investors in emerging market fixed-income securities and the country risk analysis techniques used to evaluate emerging market economies © CFA Institute. For candidate use only. Not for distribution.</p>
			</abstract>
		</profileDesc>
	</teiHeader>
	<text xml:lang="en">
	</text>
</TEI>
